miele.com 2005-04-03

# Miele, Inc.: Your Privacy

|    
---  
Residential Appliances  
  |  |     
---  
PRIVACY POLICY   
   
Miele, Inc. ("Miele") is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read this privacy policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of this website (the "Site"). This privacy policy is only applicable to the information we collect from the Site. This privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.   

  1. What this privacy policy covers
  2. Information collection & use
  3. Information sharing & disclosure
  4. Cookies
  5. IP Addresses

| 

  6. Links to other sites
  7. Security & integrity of information
  8. Retention of information
  9. Your privacy choices
  10. Questions or suggestions

  1. WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the Site. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Miele does not own or control or of people whom Miele does not manage or employ.   
Top
  2. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

We collect personally identifiable information when you send us requests for information through our Site. We may also collect information from our affiliates and third parties. 

We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser. 

We use your information for five general purposes: 

    1. To fulfill your requests for certain information and services; 
    2. To provide our services to you; 
    3. To contact you about our services and related services; 
    4. To ensure the security of the Site, and 
    5. To share your information with our employees and affiliates to help serve you better. 
Top
  3. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

We will send personally identifiable information about you to others only when: 
    1. We have your consent to share the information; 
    2. We need to share the information to provide a service you have requested; 
    3. We need to send the information to companies or people who work on behalf of Miele to provide a service to you; 
    4. We respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal requirements; 
    5. We find that your actions on our Site violate any applicable terms of use or usage guidelines; 
    6. We need to share the information to ensure the security and accuracy of the Site; 
    7. An affiliate or third party wishes to have access to your information to provide you with goods or services which may be of interest to you. 
Please note that we may disclose personally identifiable information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that doing so would be necessary in order to comply with legal process served on us.   
Top
  4. COOKIES

Cookies are small text files that a web site can send to a user's browser for storage on the hard drive. Cookies can make use of the web easier by saving status and preferences about a web site. Generally, websites use cookies to: 
    1. Remind site owners who users are and to access user information in order to deliver a more personalized service, and 
    2. Estimate audience size. 
Each browser accessing such a site is given a unique cookie. Information collected by those cookies is sometimes called "click stream" or "click trail" and may also describe pages seen by the user and track user patterns, preferences and length of stay on a particular page. We do not currently use cookies to store or track information about you. We reserve the right to use cookies in the future, and may start to do so without prior notice to you.   
Top
  5. IP ADDRESSES

When a web browser requests a web page or e-mail from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called an Internet Protocol Address ("IP Address"). We collect IP Addresses through the Site. Those IP Addresses may be used for various purposes, including, but not limited to: 
    1. Diagnose service or technology problems that are associated with the IP Addresses; 
    2. Estimate the number of users visiting the Site; 
    3. Send the most appropriate marketing, advertising or services information; or 
    4. Assist companies or persons who provide information in our service to track visits to their pages. 
  
Top
  6. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

We may provide links to external sites as a convenience to you. When you click on any such link, you will leave the Site. The inclusion of any such link does not imply Miele's endorsement of the owner or operator of the external site, the external site itself, or the products or services that the external site describes, promotes or sells. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external sites. Our privacy policy does not apply to any external site, and Miele is not responsible for the accuracy of any content supplied via any such external site. Should you rely upon that content, or otherwise use it in any way, you do so at your own risk.   
Top
  7. SECURITY AND INTEGRITY OF INFORMATION

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us, and we treat our data as assets that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ reasonable and customary information-security techniques, but no security system is capable of meeting all anticipated or unanticipated security needs. MIELE DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT ITS SECURITY SYSTEMS WILL BE FOOLPROOF OR ABLE TO FULFILL ANY ESSENTIAL PURPOSE, OR THAT YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WILL BE PROTECTED AGAINST LOSS, MISUSE OR ALTERATION BY THIRD PARTIES.   
Top
  8. RETENTION OF INFORMATION

We retain your personally identifiable information, as necessary, for business purposes and as required by law and government regulation. We reserve the right, however, to dispose of records and delete information from time to time, without prior notice.   
Top
  9. YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES

Before submitting personally identifiable information on the Site, you will be given the option of opting in for the future receipt of informational and promotional e-mails from Miele, its affiliates, subsidiaries, and business partners. 
    1. To opt in: 

Fill out the form on [this page](http://www.miele.com/emailtomiele/emailusform.asp?contact_dept_id=4&toemail=webmastr%40mieleusa%2Ecom&dept_name=Webmaster). You must check either one or both of the final two checkboxes to be notified when: 
      1. We introduce new products or services 
      2. We host events in your area. 
    2. If you have so opted in and would like to opt out: 
      1. Click [here](http://www.miele.com/newsletter/unsubscribe.asp?newsletter_type=p) to opt out of our new products and services mailing list 
      2. Click [here](http://www.miele.com/newsletter/unsubscribe.asp?newsletter_type=e) to opt out of our events mailing list 
The links above lead to pages where you must input your email address into a form. Upon clicking the submit button, the form will either remove your email address and confirm your removal, or it will indicate your address was not found in our database. 
You can always contact us in order to: 
    1. Delete your personally identifiable information from our systems, or 
    2. Update your personally identifiable information previously provided to us. 
To do so, contact the [webmaster](http://www.miele.com/emailtomiele/emailusform.asp?contact_dept_id=4&toemail=webmastr%40mieleusa%2Ecom&dept_name=Webmaster).   
Top
  10. QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS

If you have any questions or suggestions, please contact the [webmaster](http://www.miele.com/emailtomiele/emailusform.asp?contact_dept_id=4&toemail=webmastr%40mieleusa%2Ecom&dept_name=Webmaster).   
Top

Last updated: December 19, 2003.
